Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Benefit And Pension Plans For the Employes of International Harvester Corporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Benefit Plans For The Employes of International Harvester Corporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Harvester Industrial Council Tractor Works, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
    May 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Unstoppable The Story of the Harvester Strike, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
    August 21- November 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Status of Unions And Contracts Steel Division, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: History of Last Step Written Grievance Answers UAW-AFL-CIO Local Unions - Manufacturing Operations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
    February 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: International Harvester Company, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Ninth Annual Report Of The Employes' Benefit Association International Harvester Corporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Tenth Annual Report Of The Employes' Benefit Association International Harvester Corporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Annual Report of Employes' Mutual Benefit Association, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
    February 1-January 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Harvester Industrial Council, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
    March 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Harvester Worker, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
    June-July. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Unstoppable The Story of the Harvester Strike, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
    August 21 - November 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Harvester Industrial Council New Plan Has Been Adopted by Nineteen Plants, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: Memo To Subscriber, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Why does the UAW strike go on?, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Electronic Data Processing Center, Publication (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: History and Development of International Harvester, Publication (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Plans, Preparations, and Execution of International Harvester's Plant Move from Auburn, N.Y., Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    August 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 1953 Annual Report, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Annual Report 1952, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Annual Report 1957, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Annual Report 1959, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: About People, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: News-Letter To Employes In Military Service, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: To All Engineering Department Employes, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    October 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: To All West Pullman Works People, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    October 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: News, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    November 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: News, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: To All Employes of The Farm Equipment Division:, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 13: News, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 14: News, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    February 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: News, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    February 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: News, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    January 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Annual Report 1960, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 18: Today, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 19: Christmas, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 20: To All Indianapolis Works Employes and Your Families:, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    January 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Management Bulletin, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    March 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Managerial News Letter, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    March 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Managerial News Letter, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 24: Milwaukee Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    April 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Sprinfield Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    February 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Springfield Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    November 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Farmall Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    June 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Fort Wayne Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    May 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Farm Equipment Research And Engineering Center Managerial News-Letter, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    May 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Rock Falls Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    May 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Farmall Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    May 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Milwaukee Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 33: East Moline Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 34: Memphis Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    January 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: To Our Former Co-Workers:, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    January 12. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: your ideas are worth money, Publication (Box 27, Folder 17)
    January 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: New Ideas Plan and Management Recognition Plan Policy and Procedures Manual Works, Publication (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Harvester New Ideas Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1956, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    October 331. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Harvester World, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Harvester World, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    July-August. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: 1955 Annual Report, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: International Harvester World, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: International Harvester World 1964, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    By John Peterson. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: annual report 1963, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Organization Changes, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Organization Changes, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    September, October. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: $2 Billion Year In Prospect, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    March 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Spotlight for retired International Harvester people, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    April 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Spotlight for retired International Harvester people, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: IH Facts, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 14: Fort Wayne Operations IH News, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: Tractor Works Bulletin, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: To All International Harvester Managerial People:, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    April 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: To International Harvester Managerial People:, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 18: International Harvester Managerial People:, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 19: To All Canton Works Employes, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    February 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: To All Farmall Works People, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    April 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: To All Memphis Works Employes, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 22: To Employes In Military Service, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 23: Tractor Works Product Activity Bulletin, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 24: Safety Bulletin, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 25: g.o. newsletter, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 26: Memphis Works News, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    April 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Canton Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 28: Springfield Works Managerial News-Letter From the Office of the Works Manager, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 29: American Trucking Economic Giant, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 30: Harvester World, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 31: Harvester World, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    September-October. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: To All Harvester People, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    February 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: You are the Harvester Company, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    May 24. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: International Join Conference Council, Publication (Box 27, Folder 19)
    November 15. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: International Labor Organization, Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: A Great Adventure Of Our Time, Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: The ILO and Women, Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: ILO, Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: The Human Needs Of Labor, Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: International Labour Standards, Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Safety and Health of Workers, Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: ILO, Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: The ILO And Asia, Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Box: 27, folder: (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Invitation & Programme International Management Congress, Publication (Box 27, Folder 21)
    September. Item is in English; French; Dutch.
- Box: 28, folder: 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Summary of Retiree Medical Plan For Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    January 1. Item is in English; French; Dutch.
  - Item 2: Summary of Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees of International Minerals & Chemical Corporation, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Summary of Retirement Plan for Hourly Employees of International Minerals & Chemical Corporation, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Summary of Group Insurance Plan For Employees of International Minerals & Chemical Corporation (Canada) Ltd., Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Summary Of Group Insurance Plan for Employees of International Minerals & Chemical Corporation, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Paid-Up At Retirement, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Summary Of Retiree Medical Plan For Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: IN Manitoba, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Triangle, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: INCO Nickel News, Publication (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: International Paper Company Sixty-first Annual Report 1958, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Tower, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: International Paper Company Fifty-Third Annual Report 1950, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: the TiP, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Kraftsmen Chatter, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The Log of Long-Bell, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Partner, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: International Paper Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The Log, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
    January-February. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Scroll, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Pardners, Publication (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: You And International Paper, Publication (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Otis Division, Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: "Paper in the Making" Mobile Mill, Publication (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Hospital And Surgical Benefits For Employees At Southern Eligible Plants Of The International Paper Company And Optional Hospital And Surgical Benefits For Their Dependents, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Group Hospital-Surgical Major Medical Plans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Group Insurance Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Optional Additional Accidental Death And Dismemberment Insurance, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Salary Continuance Long Term Disability Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Employees' Retirement Plan Of International paper Company, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: optional additional Life Insurance benefits, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Facts About Your Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Employees' Retirement Plan of International Paper Company, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
    January 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Facts About the Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Employees' Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Kraftsman Special Feature: How IPCF Is Helping Our Community Schools, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Your Quarter Century Society, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: A Summary Of The International Paper Company Foundation Program To Help Public Secondary Schools At The Start Of The 1958-59 School Year, Publication (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Labor Agreement, Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)
    June 1, Mary 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Agreement, Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Insider, Publication (Box 28, Folder 8)
    November 24. Item is in English.
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention Program, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Long Term Disability, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Group Insurance Program, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Your Company Your Job Your Benefits, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Distribution List For Corporate Industrial Relations Manual, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Your Company Your Job Your Benefits, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Group Insurance Program, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: In The Matter In Arbitration Between International Salt Company Avery Island Mine And Refierny And International Chemical Workers Union Local 27, Publication (Box 28, Folder 10)
    August 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Int the Mater of the Arbitration Between International Salt Company and Excavating, Building Material Construction Drivers And Race Track Employees, Local No. 436, Affiliated With International Brotherhood Of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen And Helper, Publication (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Public Relations Department, Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: News Bulletin, Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: From the desk of Henry Rand, Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: The Clipping Exchange, Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Press Kit The SAFEty SHOE story, Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: How Shoes Are Made, Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: People And Shoes Seen In The News, Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
    October 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Let's Make a Shoe, Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Let's Make a Shoe, Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Application, Publication (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Information For Employees, Publication (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Information For Employees, Publication (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Change of Status, Publication (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Finance, Publication (Box 28, Folder 13)
    August 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: International Shoe Company 48th Annual Report 1959, Publication (Box 28, Folder 13)
    February 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: International Shoe Company, Publication (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Your Group Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Your Pension Benefits, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Shoes thru the ages, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Refining of Copper At The Raritan Copper Works, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: You And Your Job at Raritan Copper Works Perth Amboy New Jersey, Publication (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Order, Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
    September 11. Item is in English.
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Interstate Finance Corporation, Publication (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Employee Insurance Program, Publication (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Available IBA Tools, Publication (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Investment Company Institute Annual Report 1962, Publication (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: You and the I.D.S. Employees' Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Employers Handbook, Publication (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Statement of Company Policy, Publication (Box 28, Folder 24)
    April 4. Item is in English.
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Resource Book on Opportunities in Apprenticeship and Skilled Traddes in Iowa, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Governor's Letter to Dropouts, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Handbook for Estimation of Labor Supply for Use of a Community Survey, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Mobile Manpower Information Center, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Combination Sheltered Work and Career Motivation Programs, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Job Vacancies in Iowa Manufacturing Establishments, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: On-The-Job Training, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: Comprehensive Advisory Program to Encourage Equal Employment Opportunity: Compliance with Federal Contract Requirements Contract Compliance, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: Iowa Crime Commission, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: A Comprehensive Statewide Program To Combat Alcoholism in Iowa, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 11: Youth Opportunity Campaign 1967, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 12: Governor's Guest Program, Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Item 13: Operation: Youth Opportunity Community Improvement, Inc., Publication (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Interim Report, Publication (Box 28, Folder 26)
    June 1, December 31. Item is in English.
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Employment Benefits Handbook, Publication (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Interim Report, Publication (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Personnel, Publication (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Dear Miss Eckert, Publication (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: You And Your Job, Publication (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Agreement, Publication (Box 28, Folder 32)
    April 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Fifty Pciket Building Site, Publication (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: A Group Insurance Plan for Membres of Ithaca Gun Company, Inc., Publication (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: You and Your Job At The Ithaca Gun Co., Inc., Publication (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: You And Your Job At The Ithaca Gun Co., Inc., Publication (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Constitution And By-Laws, Publication (Box 28, Folder 36)
    August 10. Item is in English.
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Crusader, Publication (Box 28, Folder 37)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: The Jewish Hospital 114th Annual Report 1964, Publication (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Contact: A Disrict Agency Communication On Labor-Management Developments, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Contact: A District Agency Communication On Labor-Management Developments, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: YOU, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: YOU, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 5: YOU, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 6: Contract Ratified, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 7: YOU, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 8: YOU, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 9: The John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 10: YOU, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 11: Congratulations, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 12: John Hancock Patriot, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 13: John Hancock Patriot, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 14: Your Suggestion System At John Hancock, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 15: You, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Item 16: News Weekly, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
    November 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: John Hancock in 1965 A Report To Members Of The Home Office, Publication (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefits Stretch, Publication (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Item 2: Retirement Pension Plan For Agents In District Offices, Publication (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Item 3: Retirement Pension Plan For Home Office Employees And District Office Staff, Publication (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Item 4: Your Security Program At The John Hancock, Publication (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Item 5: Your Security Program At The John Hancock, Publication (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Item 6: Your Security Program At The John Hancock, Publication (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Item 7: Your Security Program At The John Hancock, Publication (Box 28, Folder 40)
- Box: 28, folder: (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Retirement Pension Plan For Agents In District Offices, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 2: Let's Get Acquainted, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 3: A Career in Life Insurance, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Item 4: it happens all the time, Publication (Box 28, Folder 41)